{
    "subject": "Prince_Tomohito_of_Mikasa",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Princess_Tomohito_of_Mikasa",
    "human_readable": "Prince Tomohito of Mikasa is married to Princess Tomohito of Mikasa.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.986968994140625,
            "question": "Who is married to Princess Tomohito of Mikasa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9865080118179321,
            "question": "What is the full name of the prince married to Princess Tomohito of Mikasa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9722293615341187,
            "question": "Are Prince Tomohito and Princess Tomohito of Mikasa related?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.947817325592041,
            "question": "Is there a shared title between Prince Tomohito and Princess Tomohito of Mikasa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.946774959564209,
            "question": "What is the relationship status of Prince Tomohito and Princess Tomohito of Mikasa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7284923195838928,
            "question": "To what royal family do Prince and Princess Tomohito belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6335992813110352,
            "question": "Does the name 'Tomohito' appear in both the prince and princess's names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15147922933101654,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about the royal family they belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0687771812081337,
            "question": "What are some common practices or traditions within their royal family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.026032784953713417,
            "question": "Is there any historical significance associated with their names or titles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Prince Tomohito of Mikasa is married to Princess Tomohito of Mikasa.",
            "html": "yago_7637_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common practices or traditions within their royal family?",
            "html": "yago_7637_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more details about the royal family they belong to?",
            "html": "yago_7637_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the name 'Tomohito' appear in both the prince and princess's names?",
            "html": "yago_7637_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7637_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7637_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7637_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7637_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7637_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7637_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7637_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7637_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7637_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7637_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The information in the documents supports the triple.\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not support the triple \"Prince Tomohito of Mikasa is married to Princess Tomohito of Mikasa.\" The relevant document states that Prince Tomohito of Mikasa was married to Nobuko As\u014d, and that his widow is referred to as Princess Tomohito of Mikasa. Therefore, they are not currently married but were previously joined in matrimony, and she is now his widow."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\"output\": \"no\"}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Context information states Princess Tomohito of Mikasa was married to Prince Tomohito of Mikasa.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Prince Tomohito of Mikasa is married to Nobuko As\u014d, who was awarded the title \"Princess Tomohito of Mikasa\" after her marriage. Princess Tomohito of Mikasa refers to the individual herself, not her husband.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}